(Sheldon:)I'm confused. Was there
some sort of peer-review committee...
(Sheldon:)...to determine which scientists
would be included?
(Raj:)Peer review? It's People magazine.
People picked me.
- What people?
- The people from People.
What? Yeah, but exactly
who are these people?
What are their credentials?
How are they qualified?
(Sheldon:)What makes accidentally noticing
a hunk of rock...
(Sheldon:)...that's been traipsing around
the solar system for billions of years...
(Sheldon:)...more noteworthy than any other scientific
accomplishment by someone under 30?
Boy, I bet Ellen Page's friends
aren't giving her this kind of crap.
(Leonard:)You proud of yourself?
(Sheldon:)In general, yes.